That guys in UP Akshay Kumar,
which market has been
looted, do it
[music] If it has happened then our
father is angry, we will
keep you on the way, we will rescue you, will you
finish your work or will you suffer after washing the mill,
Ajay should
now be halved, welcome and corrupt
[praise]
[music]
Jhaal that
Uthappa will kiss the moon, we will become Chauharmal,
today we will open the spread, it looks great, the heat will meet, I will
mix it up and put it on him tomorrow morning
[music] We will
start the above welcome, problem
Jhaal pass, do it,
my greetings to the specific, Sharp, I am Sharad talking to me,
after Pack India's Conclave Chapter Three,
we are going ahead with Mental India Kun This is
presented by James Group of
Institutions Insurance Partner LIC Jeevan
Shanti Policy
Okay, okay I am not welcoming you alone,
our three, my Brian Adams Sharp,
we welcome you,
and also welcome our 35 million national sir,
which is spread across 15 cities
through 22 radio stations
Join us and today in India's class, one
such champion is with us, who had
faith in himself and whose loved ones had faith in him
and that is why he kept achieving great things in his life.
Spider Channel is with us today, the
lion of Indian cricket, Yuvraj Singh Sushil. It
starts like this, a small child is
training in Chandigarh's cricketing academy with children much older than him.
He is scared of fast bowling but
his father tells the bowlers to
put a bomb on him, sir. Now this frightened child
reaches his father and says,
father, should I wear a helmet? Do you know what father does,
beware, when Vivian Richards did
not wear a helmet, then how will you wear it?
Yograj Singh has thrown away the fear from his heart every day.
Son Yuvraj Singh has become Yuvraj Singh, is
n't it Tulsi? Earlier, the team had lost the final.
These days, questions were being showered on the team
and only then has the patience come in the team.
Grandfather has waved his T-shirt in the stadium
that in the 2011 T20 World Cup, he hit
six sixes in six balls against England. In the 2011 World
Cup, Yuvraj Singh  Singh scored 362 runs
Chawla won the final match awards, took 15 wickets
and was named Player of the Tournament.
This is undoubtedly the most important success of Yuvraj Singh's life. The
biggest challenge here is
that in the same year Yuvraj was diagnosed with cancer. On
one hand, he was the biggest
player of 2011 and on the other hand, his life was standing at a crossroads. But
right now, Yuvraj Singh,
he has neither left the cricket field nor the field of
life. Whether it is
good or bad, Yuvraj Singh has
always been a student.
[Praise]
Ajit Hello everyone, you are a champion, we
know that the whole world accepts this,
but today I will make you talk about one of the
champions in his own field. The member of the team
is Deepak Gupta ji, he is the
President of James Group of
Institutions.
Whenever a
student passes out from Deepak Institute, he has two bats in his hand, the
first one is for domain
knowledge
and the second one is for emotional knowledge
and when he goes to James Institute with both these bats  When
students come out,
they hit sixes and fours in the field of life,
so please welcome Deepak ji, I had seen the fonts of India, that
Yuvraj Kshetra Act and very very
big fan of yours, as much as you see, I did
not remember all the brothers, Vighna
laptop Batman Shoaib Varsha Nazar Singh and 60
Sounth Ek Spoon Family function Adhuri, now let me
introduce you to the next member of the
back team,
his name is Sanjeev Mantri, he is the Executive
Director of ICICI Lombard,
one thing which is very interesting that is happening
in our country right now is that people have
understood that general insurance,
mediclaim insurance is not a fault, in
fact, it is a good investment, so you people have
understood that like a friend, he is helping them to bounce back,
that friend is the one
who puts his hand on your shoulder and says that you go and do
your job, you don't have to take any risk, I am with you, and
Sanjeev Mantri and ICICI Lombard are fulfilling this promise very well, a very warm
welcome to you Sanjeev,
you can stay like this  Have you ever met him before
for the method that Meghnad
is the time giver, then the next member of the interesting show
is this motivational speaker, social repairing
and he is there
and God has
surrounded him with more than one challenge, first his younger
sister was murdered, his mother got paralysis, his
father got TV, with great difficulty he had
built a house, it was
demolished, he was surrounded by such troubles,
so he started social service,
today he has fed this cup of milk to more than 20 lakh people, he
runs an initiative named Means of,
he has touched lakhs of people during the VAT crisis,
but one more thing which will touch your heart,
he will tell you about Anchal,
but after some time in the morning, leave it,
surprise, right,
meanwhile Yuvraj Singh's favorite events of
vitamins, which yogi is my favorite in
English, he did it after cancer, that in
English, all the joinings after cancer,
the best innings have come, it had happened  Due to
which this is very amazing, this is your
team, this solution and today Badshah is
seen coming out of the earth, we will try to know
how you
faced the challenge in your life, along with this we will
also understand from Sanjeev Bhai, Deepak Bhai and Aanchal how
they handled that 4 inch thing in their life, so
first let
us go to your early days Ajay, when we
think of cricket, now if we
think of cricketing memory, then first of all we
remember your six sixes, that is one thing
and it was imprinted in our mind, but
what is your first cricketing memory, that was
very disgusting for me, but
you will take the post memories, so
in childhood I saw you running behind the house,
rather without pads, don't love, without
helmet, and behind the house there was a
road on the side of the garden, that happens very rarely with the tiger also
and a good friend bought it and by
subscribing you will keep getting
₹50 for a month, so
we sat and hit a lot of fours and sixes with it,
we played a match after the meeting, so
I thought that she had left her husband and
looted the house  Our old man went inside and sat down
and took that bag and went with me,
who is he, he used to live in front of us, if you have
requested then please for half an hour now
this is such a thing which is
connected with you, speaking to you, I have
wanted to ride a bicycle since childhood and after buying it I will
learn to ride it for half the price myself, I have
not taken help from anyone, so
what happened Paaji, please tell me, it must be
5 years old, I have taken this
mother bicycle which I have brought home and
before she came I caught the bicycle and
I brought it to come out and I tried to
balance it a bit, it was fun, then the
road was in front and the whole road was good,
I took two
loots, 100 grams, there were torn strips on the double mark from
here and you did not like it a bit in your childhood,
father had said that if you have
any thoughts other than cricket then
see, in such a situation your debut happened in 1997
against Odisha, do you have memories of that
or egg loot, hey member of Navjot Singh
Sidhu of Punjab and the match is over  Went and
subscribe is also smaller than me
[Music]
looti game you choose OTP m99 movies fair
after 2017 sentiment I am good
Sanjeev Rai ch Deepak Bhai let me tell you that
UP's father Yograj Singh ji was a very
strict master he was never happy with UP's performance
brother tell me some stories
Right in India final was going on in father's power
if member Bihar
support 307 ji if a correct distance and option
president side love report ants I don't see
58th Punjab school exactly my
father 358
13 how many did the opposition make 350 70
who said Meghnad good but
children should when fathers talk too much about
how to maintain Awadhi how do you do
withdrawal oo think we something free mode on
200 ko what thing cricket reason wasted something which should be
you then fun
girls in such a situation children become very
spoiled this channel for the company
join cricket record breaking
records and from 10 top clicks
Mash every office in these junior cricket,
if there was something like cigarettes in junior cricket, then
I was like that it is into disuse and
this is very how you run a channel and the
interesting thing Deepak ji is doing right now is
that Deepak ji decided that we should
work more on emotional intelligence than domain knowledge
because children are going through emotional
stress at this time, so we started focusing on how to
bring positivity and optimization,
we came to know about it, if we investigated more about this then
many interesting things came out,
Deepak ji you would like to share with UP, in
this way
these children have to work on optional string, that is basically
when this model was done, we used to get a
lot of calls from students and their parents,
what should we do with the children so that they
remain busy and do not remain in mental stress and we
also used to talk related to their course curriculum, so
I made the parents and
students understand that my country is going through a hard
time but Angry Birds is now totally
new things not only for India but for the
world too  I have told you that it is most important for the
forest officer
that not only about himself,
we have to see from within that how many stones are there in the temple, so for that
we got them to do some intense
activities, told them about Bhagavad Gita,
told them about Ramayana and made them
literate that as long as you respect your parents and teachers
and
say only good things about them, then
you will mostly become more capable of them, so for that
we organised 20
to 25 hours of classes for them and made them
talk to some qualified spiritual gurus, our
teachers taught them, what happened from that is that
they mostly became strong and
we also told them that
people in the committees around you who are facing problems
or who do not have these things, they should
share it with them, so what
happened from that was that their energy got channelised,
they made lunch packets on their own, made
tablets, made meat, the children started
our fashion design department, so here the
children took their own initiative.
Sarchu himself did it for the lower side and
he did it directly with us
under his guidance, our teachers were also present, we were more so brother-in-law very very happy,
you recharge on, all this mental
stress is killed by all these things, so
this emotional psychological for them,
I say this tanning was very
necessary at this time and I
always tell them one thing that if this
child gets depression, I
told them this disease
is not of India, because of western culture,
today our children will get
depression, we have so many people to
talk about this, so many of our backers,
parents, brothers, friends, so this
thing like depression cannot happen to children in our India, so they
read it on Facebook or Google, then after that they
think that we should also
help them a lot in this way
and in this tomato research 95 percent of a
hundred percent happy and don't say damn, don't have any kind of
Fear So let's take a
small break on this note We will return
very jealous of India abroad Conclave
Chapter Feminine Yuvraj Singh Tune
Life blossoms Hope has built a home
Small efforts make me fly I am
not afraid of challenges Tests do
n't seem impossible
Sometimes there is a procession of happiness Sometimes there are delicate
moments Thankfully LIC is
always with you in the journey of life and even after that Where there is
life, there is LIC with life too
After life Hello my name is Vishal and you are watching
India's Cream Free Yuvraj
Presented by Gems Group of
Institutions
Insurance Partner LIC Jeevan Shanti
Polish
Before leaving this time let me tell you how
your cricketing career
started and after that you kept progressing
and very soon you were included in the India Under-19
World Cup squad and
you give such a performance in that, hard work that people become
serious and get noticed And
you can select the guys in the
ICC Knockout Trophy in Nairobi  You join
and then the
Indian captain Sourav Ganguly plays a
prank on Yuvraj Singh, what is that medicine
that called Sourav the night of the [ __ ] Sourav and said to
open it, if there is a
problem then tell him to follow, open a running
reminder, open tomorrow,
now I have given one, after that I have not come,
sister ji has played speed 140 McGrath world
class bullet songs like a country for
online, a
revenge well, John should not come,
I am doing it myself, then
Brett Lee played Bigg Boss run innings on alien girls,
anti-country setup notice,
Yuvraj Singh felt that this star has
felt this, I said this is the
same, then play this game, were
not arrived in India with the
championship India-Australia match,
and Akash and just realized soul and
tricks mobile and you had put one more condition
when he returned, you said that both
Dragon Singh and you should be present at Chandigarh airport
to receive new
updates, this is a completely different reason, dormant because but
father or mother has been  Fighting like
cats and dogs sewer like printed
white this movement in odisha and violence clean
family gathering family Gonu lot
in reform act great moment with a
smile thrown at the length mark and both are
fighting I want this back
now let's go I
was trying to do it in 2002 I did match fixing these
people's trust was lost they were
playing the final at Lord's were on the field in the last 9 finals
and Mohammad Kaif
made an entry that was the time when Sachin so I should leave the public
that Khajur Roy almost go away you will do something
okay
and torque sound set car Ramvilas
95060 pressure of innovative and creative
expressions iron your brother you and
Mohammad Kaif played a brilliant innings
of 121,066 runs played a brilliant innings of 325 runs did not make a
milestone for Indian cricket
which after that to deal with it please subscribe a new
and you say that
Sourav Ganguly has a
big hand in this trust
that was looted  Guddu issued a
warning a dream new
delhi delhi and dropped united asli ke yaar isko
kaise bola diya main team me reh rahe
ho
hello viewers your skin from them a
relationship such a ban gaya with the page that
you can space in the place and then your
own PM in waiting for your
valuable feedback that you did not belong to that era
friend this is my ko team hue din
16 out of 16 chola to ladke hawas lene chahiye
team mein required tak promised you
23.12 level profile 23share to 9.39
mids of things always encourage people to speak to
connect with whoever you subscribe to is
important very very part of the medical
insurance is
your channel health insurance business so
whatever daily bhaav with everything about and
philosophy that you have tell us about it it is
important to reach out to us it is
resting on line for this facility
Shraddha prospective see the question paper
and finally Bigg Boss ko  Security in terms
of service and things right from
your family health
quiz always very well no difficult moment
water and economic and financial
burden which is related activating intervention the
current crisis has been extremely
difficult to live with water has certainly not given
women more than 100 importance of health
insurance agar kuch test bataye critical
penetration and 30 countries around point
like GDP global average distance to be
dead play 50 to constipation important explain
the blue line don't have enough money to drawing
and not be possible way a very very funny
subscribe our back cutting
is stupid ansh events like this is it to
draw a job to see useless jewellery making
changes to get a clear return to Google Play Store
Play Store appealed that they
believe in the company of the individual and
subscribe candy crush elements very very
love you
a placebo controlled end  Divided of way not saying
no challenge of the defense in
opinion religious understanding times but
with intent and ability both are intact
make things happen as per the provisions are
relevant voice rupee sir yes I don't know
next videos opportunity not soil I
heard somewhere that you proposed to your wife
how did you propose to the gentleman suit
medical moment how did you
add them
and when I came to my senses then in front of me the ring was
kept on the commission wow what
Magh month they will give me a
and I had to go and sit on the same loot temple some
confused Sanjay Colony Yogi has to be put the
problem of hatred of girls ok
you must be thinking that six sixes were hit or a
little behind that before that some villager hit
six sixes in the last over
our lion got injured to 2007 South
Africa T20 World Cup India's team got
trapped in England's team ringtone
tell me the further story some talks are going on
a friend for every state  Elections its
top five - In the sixth decade of my age,
I got a mental
[laughs]
signal from Ismail outside that 56
calculations are equal, what is the matter, in 2010 I had a cervical
problem, I used to have pain and in such a situation,
in 2010, for the first time in my 10 year career,
you were dropped from the team,
but they say that whenever Kishore takes two steps
back, he has to take the biggest leap of his life
and that is what he did,
you were included in the 2011 World Cup squad, the
performance you gave, the
whole of India can never forget, 362
runs, 15 wickets, 42 matches, awards and player
of the team, after 28 years, thanks to your print
performance, once you returned to India on the World Cup, is there any
question that does not disturb you in the year,
scientists work that his dreams come true
and all that you find yourself in, if the country
wins the Twenty20 World Cup, then you
Meghwal Meghwal at the time  People did
not talk to each other, they were all hugging each other.
What happens here is that if there is a
small role, it turns out
that we are using each other too. Don't
forget that there is a cat, from cats
to the passengers in Delhi, all these things happen a lot,
so the update with the movement and style, that
beautiful moment today, everyone here was
playing Candy Crush with each other,
selling it to each other, hugging each other, so this is
a summary of chapters that happened in 2009, we have to see the
increase in memory and almost each of these
companies from Kiran More Sports
Management Company's shares too, today
is the final product announced, it only gives
roof and avoid you cannot refrain from
people will make them under 6000.
Half the final product will increase the food habits,
Aman Laddu judgment in year follow-up
comments or who knows that Aamir is
interested in cricket, I am
asked at least 10 times, so Ayush really talking Tencent
is an option, I have to go, I will
try it in our flour  finally dedicated faith in
this discussed polytechnic stand
matter and was ridden in the state
governments should not be used in this match to
turn on office not delhi tennis club
skin and unfortunately r eyes like rudra
stadium in
absolute truth means in english cigarette of
the match brother arrested reaching home and night
record south africa rus wedding bank
whos people contest this migration
certificate setting is helpful b ka ward no
mumbai rape cases of adverse but you will give
computer industry amazing to reach to leave his
promise you see your soul and
remember your heart pumping of pimples
bearing and this movement but i love you thank you so much
for giving me this bible important hearing has
started and can mean a lot more wow
[laughs]
well whatever you have said at this time let me tell you
that in 2011 i am working
that there are forces behind it and to back to very
special about which i came to know made
this  Point to you Vismo Shabnam, there was something
lying on it in the room, so let's take it
out, I would love to get Lucky
Ali's blessings for it. I was one of
those people, so he was
sitting at a table,
I kept it in front of him, I said Guruji, is
this going for a cup,
bless this, he said, okay,
how can I bless this, by placing my hands like this, Bhole, the rest of the organizations,
everyone's base people, by touching their hands, that's it, then
what was decided, you went and sat on that bed, I took it
and he gave it to him, when I got it on the
day of England, then Banna, when it
came in my hand, what did I feel, I have bread
in my hand, a friend at number two, helmet
number one, this number two on the right,
and I remember it very well,
in the middle of the World Cup, well, before the South Africa match,
and Sachin went, a former lawyer, he is a renowned
expert in repairing
illegal constructions, well,
if you or you are playing for you, then he
added the fast, she said, what's the matter, in
October 2011, did you come to know that you have a
tumor in me, you went through a lot of difficulties, the
name was that subscribe and  January 2012, after
reaching the doctor's clinic, drink that juice which is
full of balls, how to print words, you are at the
peak of your career, such things happen
[music]
then placed a question for treatment of
125, both of them have
possible time, pure Hindustan
Jobs in Hindi dubbed, absolutely buzz  The office look
at the best scenes of cancer in India live very very
happy that you can listen songs
office list me do subscribe
hain and country certain areas ashok kumar
das policies and we don't have structure for
cancer symptoms do something for below poverty
line hai
that ad ad saree ka pura programs with
foundation and not to listen to that
[music]
so are you from pimples to injured duplicate
hain
that a bada ki madam ke inch mantra or hate kate main
aapse that ki zindagi ka ek panna zindagi ki aarzoo hamessa
yuvraj ne bola phir milungi that this
comes to your mind that
after that another thing happens that your
perspective of thinking changes you start
seeing positivity in everything the thing was
interesting doctor then two
people around you started saying that does she have an answer
now or not she comes in so decorated toh
front part taraf ice protests from
Africa everything positivity in Indian
Railways should not possible without any rule
foundation and subscribe
that eye flu  Withdrawal inch good position obscene
country countries square people who need support
you in every corporate holidays
college supporter NGO like positively and
helps people in need to change situation loot
kya bagh solid stop this cream easily
so let's cut this point
let's all do this together Sanjeev Deepak Samay
Salute
song Jai Hind wala 60 Fantastic Eid thank you thank you
for being subscribed thank you for
watching my video love oo
jhal